Abhishek Malakar

Full Stack Developer

Contact

Moble: 7748057369, 9340639478

E-mail: ABHIMALIM@GMAIL.COM

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/abhishek-malakar8aa16a190

GitHub: https://github.com/Abhishekmalakar

Summary

I have 2 years of experience includes Microsoft .NET technologies, ,Angular 2/4, Reacts. ML, Data Science. I have successfully participated in various projects based on Microsoft's software development frameworks, Reacts and database technologies. I have also done some self freelance projects.

Technical Skills

Environments	Windows
Front End Languages	Angular 2/4, Reacts, Type Script, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, , HTML, Tailwinds
Microsoft Technologies	MVC, C#, Entity-framework, Link Query
Testing Framework	N Unit, Ms Unit
Database	SQL Server
Development Tools	Visual Studio, Visual Studio code, GooleColabe, JupyterNotbook, Power-Bl.
Deployment Tools	MS Azure, GitHub,
Domains	Product-base Software, Education, Healthcare

Professional Experience

Vibrant Info-Hybrid (Software Engineer) Duration: April 2024 - Till Date

Ahemdabad

Vibrant Info providing customized solutions in accordance with specific business needs. This is where vibrant excels, seamlessly blending customer-centric encounters with cutting-edge design principles.

Project	Lawarence Technical University .NET
Summary	Experience in CMS architectures, focusing on the LTU Projects framework. Skilled in dynamic site and and page creation, delivering robust, scalable, and customizable solutions.
Main Technologies	DotNet MVC, SQL Server, Angular
Responsibilities	 Worked on memeory leak and performance improvement Designed and code the application Developed .Net APIs to meet client requirments.

Astoria Solutions -Onsite (Associate Software Engineer) Aug 2022 - Feb 2024

Hyderabad

Astoria Technologies is a specialized digital transformation with innovative solutions for safety, productivity, and

accountibility focusing on hazardous industries and foothok companies.

Project	AstorSuit (US Patented)
Summary	It is US patent technoloy product that can be individually or combined integrates with third part systems and offer customized dashboards.
Main Technologies	Angular 2, SASS, MVC, SQL Server 2008, Power-BI, ML
Responsibilities	 Developed and Integrated API's for seamless integration. Done API Unit testing and power BI Dashboards. Setup the Angular 2 component for project Managed data processing with tools like roboflow, image labelling Implement ML model to train & test image data sets.
Project	AstorTime
Project Summary	AstorTime It is a part of astorSuit us patented product that manages attendances and calculates salaries, shifts and time to ensure safety life from hazardous zones.
	It is a part of astorSuit us patented product that manages attendances and

DDUGKY (Data Science -Training) Duration : Dec 2021 – June 2022

Bhopal

Deen Dayal Upadhay Gramin Kaushalya Yojana is a govt. skill training program that provides rural candiates with offline training in advance AI and ML technologies.

Project	Time Series Model
Summary	Proficient in filtering and cleaning share market data utilizing a range of technologies to ensure data accuracy. Developed ML model to analyze share market trends and make pridictions.
Main Technologies	Python, Pandas, Numpy, Skylearn, Arima & Sarima, Google Colabe, PowerBl
Responsibilities	 Understood and analyzed the requirements Designed and coded the google collabe. Clean the data sets and remove null values. Train and test the model to apply ML algorithms. Apply statistics for pridiction data accuracy.

GMR Network (Self- Freelance Project)

www.gmrnetwork.in

Globle online reporting network is a leading teleradiology and nuclear medicine online reporting services provider, revolutionizing healthcare by bridging tha gap between image interpretation and patient care.

Project GMR Reporting	
-----------------------	--

Summary	Provding online reporting for various radiology subjects in healthcare, lincluding X-ray,CT-scanes, MRIs, and other nuclear Medicine diagnostics.
Main Technologies	Reacts, Tailwind CSS, Django, SQL Server, DCOM Viewer.
Responsibilities	 Understood the client requirements . Developed UI and Data binding with react from scratch . Organized client meeting and prepare documents.

Educational Background

■ BE (Computer Science & Engineer)—Sagar Institute of research & Technology. Year May-2020 (7.3 GPA)

Certifications/ Internships

- Data Science . Nasscom NSQF Level 08.(Offline)
- Python and Web Development Dollop Infotech Pvt Ltd.(Offline)
- Python Coding. Hacker Rank. (Online)
- Web Appliction . Coursera(University of Michigan (Online)

Personal Details

Address : Khargone, 451335 MP, India

Gender : Male
Status : Unmarried
DOB : 7 Aug 1998
Languages : English ,Hindi

Self Declaration

I, Abhishek Malakar, hereby declare that the information provided in this resume is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

